<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Snowcamp 2022</title>
    <link>https://snowcamp.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Snowcamp 2022</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr</language><atom:link href="https://snowcamp.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snowcamp.io/en/coc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowcamp.io/en/coc/</guid>
      <description>Code of conduct The Quick Version SnowCamp is dedicated to providing a harassment-free conference experience for everyone, regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), or technology choices. We do not tolerate harassment of conference participants in any form. Sexual language and imagery is not appropriate for any conference venue, including talks, workshops, parties, Twitter and other online media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snowcamp.io/en/organisation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowcamp.io/en/organisation/</guid>
      <description>  Organisation  Snowcamp is a conference crafted by developers from the Grenoble area. It was started in 2016 on the initiative of AlpesJug. All organizers are enthusiast geeky volonteers.           Cédric Tran-Xuan           Johan Martinsson           Lorie Pisicchio           Ludovic Poitou           Michel Barret           Miguel Moquillon           Pierrick Rassat           Rémy Sanlaville           Sébastien Chassande-Barrioz           Yannick Chiron           Yohan Lasorsa         </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snowcamp.io/en/previous-editions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowcamp.io/en/previous-editions/</guid>
      <description>2019        How was 2019? Great with wonderful subjects!
 In 2019, SnowCamp focused on 4 themes: Discovery, Web &amp;amp; DevOps / Cloud, Languages &amp; Paradigmes and IA / Machine Learning. You can find the agenda and some slides here!
     Sponsors 2019  Without them, nothing would have been possible. A big thank you to our sponsors 2019!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snowcamp.io/en/snowcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowcamp.io/en/snowcamp/</guid>
      <description>Snowcamp  The conference driving you (wal)nuts       What is SnowCamp? First and foremost, it&#39;s a high-level technical conference that focuses on innovation. SnowCamp brings IT professionals and researchers together to discuss today&#39;s and tomorrow’s technologies. SnowCamp is a unique concept: day-long workshops on Wednesday, to learn or improve a certain technology; a more classical conference on Thursday and Friday, with the bonus of allowing participants to discover research projects through 5 minutes pitches; a socializing and relaxing day on the snow, in the mountains, on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snowcamp.io/en/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowcamp.io/en/sponsors/</guid>
      <description>Become a sponsor  Snowcamp is organized by a group of geeky volonteers. Their only motivation is to propose a unique conference gathering innovation and research. To make a success of this adventure, we need you. In return, we offer you a large visibility, on the web and during the event. It&#39;s the perfect opportunity to meet developers from Grenoble, demonstrate your products and services, and to make yourself known.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://snowcamp.io/en/tickets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snowcamp.io/en/tickets/</guid>
      <description>Tickets  You can buy a pack of 3 days (universities + conferences), or 2 days (conferences only). The tickets can be bought through our partner YouPlan. Beware, the number of attendees is limited and we were sold out last year! The store is not open yet    Early Birds - Package 3 days 150 &amp;euro; 100 &amp;euro; Universities &amp;#43; Conferences
  Access to the Universities  Access to the Conferences  Breakfast for the 3 days  Lunch for the 3 days  Meet &amp; Greet on Thursday evening  The store is not open yet    Early Birds - Package 2 days 60 &amp;euro; 42 &amp;euro; Conferences only</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
